Hey, first of all, congratulations on,
you know, getting drafted and coming to
Las Vegas. My my first question is just
just talk about could you talk about a
little bit about your skill set and what
do you feel like you you'll be provided
at the next level?
>> I mean, I just think I'm a great run
stopper. Um, great hands, great strong
point of attack and uh play with a a
tenacity that is, you know, at extremely
high level.
When you look at the Raiders defensive
line, how excited are you get to work
with some of the players that maybe
you've seen over the years like Max
Crosby?
>> Yeah, Max Crosby great and there's, you
know, plenty other great be linemen
there, great coaching staff. I just
can't wait to get down there and get to
work.
>> I had two questions for you. One, how
much did you communicate with the
Raiders in the process? And were they on
your radar in terms of teams that might
be picking you?
>> Yeah, the Raiders the Raiders were
definitely in the process. Um I met with
the Dline coach um on Zoom and you know
had good talks with the um scouts and
stuff. So I knew there it was definitely
option for them to come get me. So I'm
really excited and really happy.
>> My other question was um I know you were
a really good baseball player too and
you had the opportunity to play that
collegiately. How much thought was given
to that and I mean I guess now you're
pretty happy with the decision that you
made.
>> Yeah. 300 something plus pounds. So I
think I made the right decision to play
football and not baseball.
Yeah.
>> What would you say is one of the biggest
uh qualities that you would bring to the
locker room and the strengths that you
bring to this team?
>> Yeah, I think I'm just uh I just care
for the guys in the locker room. Um I'm
going to get there. I'm a new guy, but
you know, I'm going to love everybody
and care for everybody in the locker
room and I think that's the most
important thing and that's I think
that's the best thing I bring to the
table, just being a good person and
caring about everybody.
>> Hey Brandon, um I was reading your bio.
said you put on nearly 50 pounds when
you rolled at NC State. So like you slid
around the defensive line. I'm just
curious your experience playing, you
know, multiple positions along the D
line there.
>> Yeah, I played freaking every every
position on the D line and um I think I
found what I'm best at, which is nose
tackle and um you know, I'm just ready
to get after and get to Las Vegas.
>> Awesome. That looks like it. Thanks so
much, Brandon. Really appreciate your
time.
>> Thank y'all. Nice to meet y'all. You
have a good one.